Osborne Family Papers
Osborne Family Papers
- Organization records
  - General
    - Reform Schools, circa 1916; inmates' statements (Box 266)
    - Seymour Library Association, 1877-1904 (Box 266)
    - United Nations Relief and Rehabilitation Administration (UNRRA), 1943-1945 (Box 266)
    - United States Army
      - Pelham, Peter, 1813-1826 (Box 266)
      - Indians, slaves, recruiting and frontier posts, 1814-1822 (Box 266)
    - U.S.. Department of State
      - American Embassy, Berlin
        - Miscellaneous, 1915-1917 (Box 266)
        - Dispatches and memoranda, 1915 (Box 266)
      - American Embassy, Oslo
        - Miscellaneous, 1944-1946 (Box 266)
        - Accounts (Vol. 108), 1945-1946 (Box 267)
        - Ledger (Vol. 109), 1945-1946 (Oversize 3)
        - Printed matter, 1945-1946 (Box 267)
      - American Legation, Copenhagen
        - Dispatches and memoranda, 1917-1919; 3 folders (Box 267)
      - Office of Strategic Services (OSS), 1942-1943 (Box 267)
      - Paris Peace Conference, 1919; protocol, draft (Box 267)
    - Washington Conference on Arms Limitation, 1921-1922 (Box 267)
    - Wells College, Aurora, N.Y., 1906-1912 (Box 267)
    - Women's Educational and Industrial Union, Auburn, N.Y.
      - Miscellaneous, 1896-1944 (Box 267)
      - Fiftieth Anniversary Pageant, 1932 (Box 267)
      - Specifications and plans, 1905-1907 (Box 267)
    - Yaddo"/"Pine Garde," Saratoga Springs, N.Y., 1888-1926 (Box 267)
  - Prisons
    - Miscellaneous, 1907-1925 (Box 268)
    - Miscellaneous printed matter, 1900-1923 (Box 268)
    - American Prison Association, 1910-1941; printed material (Box 268)
    - Auburn Prison
      - Miscellaneous, 1908-1923 (Box 268)
      - Murphy, John E. ("Canada Blackie"), 1915 (Box 268)
      - Printed matter, 1879-1921 (Box 268)
    - Clinton Prison, Clinton, N.Y., 1917 (Box 269)
    - Connecticut State Prison, 1917 (Box 269)
    - Great Meadow Prison, 1915 (Box 269)
    - Illinois State Penitentiary, 1919 (Box 269)
    - Joint Committee on Prison Reform, 1914 (Box 269)
    - League for the Abolition of Capital Punishment, 1925 (Box 269)
    - Mutual Welfare League
      - National organization
        - Miscellaneous, 1918-1927 (Box 269)
        - Accounts, 1921 (Box 269)
        - By-Laws, 1920 (Box 269)
        - Description and history, 1913 (Box 269)
        - Incorporation of store, 1915 (Box 269)
        - Minutes, Board of Directors, 1928-1933 (Box 269)
        - Printed matter, 1912-1927 (Box 269)
        - Publications
          - Monthly Record, Nos. 1-12., 1920-1921 (Box 269)
          - The O.E. Library Critic, 1914-1920 (Box 269)
        - Publicity, 1915 (Box 269)
        - Reports
          - Miscellaneous, 1918-1920 (Box 269)
          - Treasurer, 1918-1932 (Box 269)
      - Auburn Chapter
        - Miscellaneous, 1913-1929 (Box 269)
        - Constitution, undated (Box 269)
        - Minutes, 1913-1914 (Box 269)
        - Publication, The Bulletin, I-III, 1914-1917 (Box 270)
      - Portsmouth, N.H. Chapter
        - Miscellaneous, 1918-1921 (Box 270)
        - Memoranda, 1918-1921 (Box 270)
        - Minutes, 1919 (Box 270)
        - Printed matter, 1919 (Box 270)
        - Publication, The Mutual Welfare News, I-V, 1917-1921 (Box 270)
      - Sing Sing Chapter
        - Miscellaneous, 1914-1921 (Box 270)
        - Finance, 1916 (Box 270)
        - Golden Rule Brotherhood, 1914-1915 (Box 270)
        - Printed matter, 1911-1930 (Box 270)
    - National Committee on Prisons and Prison Labor
      - Miscellaneous, 1913-1921 (Box 270)
      - Minutes, Executive Council, 1914-1917 (Box 271)
      - Printed matter, 1910-1931 (Box 271)
    - National Society of Penal Information
      - Miscellaneous, 1920-1924 (Box 271)
      - Finance, 1922-1926 (Box 271)
      - Handbook, state prisons, circa 1924 (Box 271)
      - Memoranda, 1923-1925 (Box 271)
      - Minutes, 1922-1926 (Box 271)
      - Printed matter, 1922-1931 (Box 271)
      - Publication, News Bulletin, I-XII, 1930-1941; 2 folders (Box 271)
      - Reports
        - Annual, 1925-1926 (Box 271)
        - State prisons, 1920-1924
          - Miscellaneous (Box 271)
          - Colorado (Box 271)
          - Connecticut (Box 271)
          - Delaware (Box 272)
          - Maine (Box 272)
          - Maryland (Box 272)
          - Massachusetts (Box 272)
          - Michigan (Box 272)
          - New Jersey (Box 272)
          - New Hampshire (Box 272)
          - New York (Box 272)
          - Pennsylvania (Box 272)
          - Rhode Island (Box 272)
          - Vermont (Box 272)
    - New York State
      - Commission of Prisons
        - Miscellaneous, 1913-1916 (Box 272)
        - Printed matter, 1906-1913 (Box 272)
        - Transcript, 1915 (Box 272)
      - House of Refuge, Randall's Island, 1916; treatment of inmates (Box 272)
      - Superintendent of Prisons, 1911-1915; prison labor (Box 272)
    - New York State Prison Council
      - Miscellaneous, 1916-1917 (Box 272)
      - Printed matter, undated (Box 273)
      - Reports, 1916-1917 (Box 273)
    - Osborne Association
      - Miscellaneous, 1933-1945 (Box 273)
      - Printed matter (Vol. 110), 1933-1938 (Box 273)
      - Reports
        - Annual, 1933-1940 (Box 273)
        - History, Organization and Accomplishments, 1930-1934 (Box 273)
        - Survey of State and Federal Institutions for Delinquent Juveniles, 1937 (Box 273)
    - Portsmouth Naval Prison, N.H.
      - Miscellaneous, 1917-1920 (Box 273)
      - Notes, Warden, 1918-1921 (Box 274)
      - Orders (leave and travel), 1917-1919 (Box 274)
      - Printed matter, 1917-1920 (Box 274)
      - Reports
        - On Alleged Conditions, 1918-1920 (Box 274)
        - Department of Justice Investigation, 1919-1920 (Box 274)
        - Discharges, 1917-1920 (Box 274)
        - Inmates' Histories, 1917-1919 (Box 275)
        - Morning reports, 1920 (Box 275)
      - Statements, 1917 (Box 275)
    - Prison Association of New York
      - Miscellaneous, 1914-1924 (Box 275)
      - Minutes, Executive Committee, 1914-1921 (Box 275)
      - Printed matter (Vols. 111-117), 1910-1940; 7 volumes (Box 275)
      - Recommendations to New York State Legislature, 1939 (Box 275)
      - Report, annual, 1934 (Box 275)
    - Prison Discipline Society, 1853-1859 (Box 275)
    - Prison Reform Commission, 1925-1932 (Box 275)
    - Sing Sing Prison, Ossining, N.Y.
      - Miscellaneous, 1839-1961 (Box 276)
      - Bulletins, 1911-1915 (Box 276)
      - Capital punishment, 1914-1916 (Box 276)
      - Chaplain, 1916 (Box 276)
      - Daily passes, 1915 (Box 276)
      - Escapes, 1914-1916 (Box 276)
      - Finances, 1898-1916 (Box 276)
      - Guards, 1915 (Box 276)
      - Health and medical, 1915-1916 (Box 276)
      - Industry and labor, 1910-1915 (Box 276)
      - Investigations, 1913 (Box 276)
      - Memoranda
        - Nos. 1-100, 1914-1915 (Box 276)
        - Nos. 101-676, 1914-1915; 6 folders (Box 277)
      - Pardons and paroles, 1903-1916 (Box 277)
      - Prisoners' statements, 1913-1923 (Box 278)
      - Printed matter, 1913 (Box 278)
      - Report by Thomas Mott Osborne on his tenure, undated (Box 278)
      - Statistics, 1910-1915 (Box 278)
      - Transfers, 1913-1916 (Box 278)
    - Welfare League Association, circa 1920 (Box 278)
- Financial records
  - Corporate
    - American Linen Fiber Company, 1913; prospectus (Box 278)
    - Auburn Hame Company, 1904; stock certificates (Box 278)
    - Auburn Iron Company, 1905-1949; yearly statements (Box 278)
    - Auburn National Bank
      - Miscellaneous, 1912-1958 (Box 278)
      - Ledger (Vol. 118), circa 1900 (Box 278)
    - Auburn Savings Bank
      - Miscellaneous, undated (Box 278)
      - History (Vol. 119), circa 1948 (Box 278)
    - Auburn Tack Company, 1888; shares (Box 278)
    - Birch Point Farm (Vol. 120), 1907-1910; accounts (Box 278)
    - Board of Education, Auburn, N.Y.
      - Art Committee accounts, 1898-1900 (Box 278)
      - Receipt, 1888 (Box 278)
    - Buffalo Transparent Products Company, Inc.
      - Miscellaneous, 1915 (Box 279)
      - Balance sheet, 1908 (Box 279)
      - Bills of sale, 1905-1915 (Box 279)
      - Production process, 1909 (Box 279)
    - Case, Bronson and Company, 1857-1859; account with the Auburn Prison (Box 279)
    - Cayuga County Dairy Company, 1907-1923 (Box 279)
    - Columbian Rope Company
      - Miscellaneous, 1907-1952 (Box 279)
      - Wage scales and union activity, 1913 (Box 279)
    - Cuban Plantations Company, 1899; prospectus (Box 279)
    - Diamond Shading Film Company, 1906-1907 (Box 279)
    - Disston and Son Saw, Tool and Steel Works, 1867; price list (Box 279)
    - Dolphin Point Association, Niles, N.Y., 1889-1905 (Box 279)
    - Eagle Wagon Works, 1910-1928 (Box 279)
    - Ellis Adding-Typewriter Company
      - Miscellaneous, 1910-1920 (Box 279)
      - Contracts, 1910-1911 (Box 279)
      - Printed matter (Box 279)
      - Statements, monthly, 1912-1914 (Box 279)
    - Freeville Inn, Freeville N.Y., 1906; specifications and contracts (Box 279)
    - International Harvester Company, 1903-1912; re purchase of D.M. Osborne & Company (Box 279)
    - John Hunter Corporation, 1913-1922 (Box 279)
    - Jefferson Theatre, Auburn, N.Y.
      - Ledger (Vol. 121), 1918-1919 (Box 279)
      - Specifications and contracts, 1909-1924 (Box 280)
    - Lisbon Oil Company, 1865 (Box 280)
    - Merchants Union Express Company, 1866 (Box 280)
    - J. H. Messenger Company
      - Printed matter, circa 1910 (Box 280)
      - Reports, 1909-1911 (Box 280)
    - D.M. Osborne & Company
      - Miscellaneous, 1865-1921 (Box 280)
      - Assets and liabilities, 1890-1895 (Box 280)
      - Bills receivable (Vol. 122), 1857-1859 (Box 280)
      - Collections department accounts and correspondence, 1906-1907 (Box 280)
      - Dividends, 1902 (Box 280)
      - Employees (Vol. 123), circa 1894 (Box 280)
      - Income and disbursements statements, 1886-1896 (Box 280)
      - Insurance, real properties, 1897-1898 (Box 281)
      - Labor relations, 1887-1913 (Box 281)
      - Machinery orders, 1897-1901 (Box 281)
      - Machinery design and construction illustrations, circa 1860-1900 (Box 281)
      - Manufacturing and sales statistics (Vol. 124), 1890-1891 (Box 281)
      - Minutes, Board of Directors (Vol. 125), 1875-1912 (Box 281)
      - Net worth statements, 1886-1899 (Box 282)
      - Newspaper clippings, 1894-1897 (Box 282)
      - Plant operations and sales statements, 1906-1912 (Box 282)
      - Real estate statements, 1873-1878 (Box 282)
      - Sales department (Vol. 126), 1888-1899 (Box 282)
      - Stock certificates (Vol. 127), 1876-1903 (Box 282)
      - Trustee account statements, 1903-1925 (Box 283)
    - Osborne Hotel, Auburn, N.Y.
      - Miscellaneous, 1887-1957 (Box 283)
      - Blueprints, 1954-1955 (Tube 1)
      - Inventory of furnishings, 1941 (Box 283)
      - Receipts, 1934-1955 (Box 283)
      - Specifications, contracts and plans, 1898-1926 (Box 283)
      - Statements, monthly, 1924-1934 (Box 283)
    - Osborne Memorial Fund, 1908-1927; contributions (Box 284)
    - Owasco Valley Oil Company
      - Miscellaneous, 1865 (Box 284)
      - Stock certificates, 1865 (Box 284)
    - Robinson Monument Company, 1908; stock transfer (Box 284)
    - Seneca Falls Woolen Company, 1908-1909 (Box 284)
    - Steam Saw-Mill Association, Manhattan Island, 1824-1825; minutes, Executive Committee (Vol. 128) (Box 284)
    - Toll-Gate Farm, 1886; inventory (Box 284)
    - Tousey Varnish Company, 1908; printed material (Box 284)
    - Transit Finance Company, 1903 (Box 284)
    - Victoria Paper Mills Company, 1917 (Box 284)
  - Personal
    - Allen, Amaziah and Willits, Abraham, undated (Box 284)
    - Baldwin, William H., 1905; memorial fund (Box 284)
    - Brister, Thomas, 1875 (Box 284)
    - Devens, Mary, 1920; inventory of estate (Box 284)
    - Gridley, Henry H., 1869; account to the Wood and Mann Steam Engine Company (Box 284)
    - Holmes, William, 1825 (Box 284)
    - Kelley, Simeon, 1849-1850 (Box 284)
    - Kirby Family, Dartmouth, N.H., 1786-1838 (Box 284)
    - Marsh, E.C., 1837-1860 (Box 284)
    - Osborne, Agnes (Devens)
      - Receiver's certificate, 1895 (Box 284)
      - Stock sale, 1886-1895 (Box 284)
    - Osborne, David Munson
      - Miscellaneous, undated (Box 284)
      - Account books (Vols. 130-134), 1847-1856; 1855,; 1874-1887; 5 volumes (Box 284)
      - Bills and receipts, 1872-1875; for house construction, Auburn, N.Y. (Box 284)
      - Cash books (Vol. 135-137), 1854-1855; 1880-1883; 3 volumes (Box 285)
      - Inventories
        - Glass, china and linen (Vols. 138-140), 1879; 1879-1882,; 1885; 3 volumes (Box 285)
        - Household furniture, 1881 (Box 285)
      - Valuation of rented properties, 1882 (Box 285)
      - Wage book (Vol. 142), 1878 (Box 285)
    - Osborne, David Munson II, 1871-1957 (Box 285)
    - Osborne, Eliza (Wright)
      - Miscellaneous, 1852-1907 (Box 285)
      - Account book (Vol. 143), 1904-1911 (Box 285)
      - Insurance policies, real estate, 1889-1902 (Box 286)
      - Inventories of furniture, 1874-1880 (Box 286)
      - Legacy, 1911-1914 (Box 286)
    - Osborne, Josephine F., 1899; stocks (Box 286)
    - Osborne, Lithgow
      - Miscellaneous, 1910-1963 (Box 286)
      - Employees: Wages and taxes (Vols. 144-145), 1953-1956; 2 volumes (Box 286)
      - Income and disbursements
        - Annual statements, 1939-1949 (Box 286)
        - Ledger (Vol. 146), 1925-1933 (Box 286)
        - Ledger (Vol. 147), 1934-1949 (Box 287)
      - Trust account report, 1936-1956 (Box 287)
    - Osborne, Lithgow Devens, 1946-1949; stock assignment (Box 287)
    - Osborne, Robert K., 1912-1916; guardianship of estate (Box 287)
    - Osborne, Thomas Mott
      - Miscellaneous, 1907-1924 (Box 287)
      - Account books
        - Auburn National Bank (Vol. 148), 1898-1901 (Box 287)
        - European travel (Vols. 149-150), 1901; 2 volumes (Box 287)
        - Howland & Clark (Vol. 151), 1898-1899 (Box 288)
      - Blueprints and specifications
        - Residence, South Street, Auburn, 1892-1912 (Box 288)
        - Residence, South Street, Auburn, circa 1895 (Oversize 1)
        - Residence, South Street, Auburn, circa 1895 (Oversize 12)
        - Residence, Willow Point, Owasco Lake, circa 1910 (Tube 2)
      - Income and disbursements
        - Ledgers
          - (Vols. 152-156), 1883; 1892-1905; 5 volumes (Box 288)
          - (Vols. 157-160), 1906-1918; 4 volumes (Box 289)
          - (Vols. 161-162), 1919-1926 (Box 290)
      - Income tax returns, 1894-1927 (Box 290)
      - Insurance policies
        - Miscellaneous, 1907 (Box 290)
        - Real property, 1896-1921 (Box 290)
      - Investment report prepared by Gerald D. Boardman, 1919 (Box 290)
      - Osborne Estate, 1927-1958 (Box 290)
      - Receipts and expenditures for The Right Way
        - Miscellaneous, 1921-1925 (Box 290)
        - Journal (Vol. 163), 1921-1925 (Box 291)
        - Ledger (Vol. 164), 1921-1925 (Box 291)
      - Royalties, 1915-1947 (Box 291)
      - Stock assignments, International Harvester Company, 1907-1908 (Box 291)
    - Osborne Family
      - Blueprints and specifications, undated; for residence, Willow Point, Owasco Lake (Box 291)
      - Household expenses
        - Ledgers
          - (Vol. 165-169), 1853-1859; 1865-1866,; 1876-1880; 5 volumes (Box 291)
          - (Vol. 170-171), 1881-1884; 1903-1906; 2 volumes (Box 292)
        - Notebook (Vol. 172), 1883 (Box 292)
      - Income and disbursements ledger (Vol. 173), 1907-1936 (Box 292)
      - Inventories
        - Household furniture, 1944-1952 (Box 292)
        - Household linen (Vol. 174), 1908 (Box 292)
        - Household silver, 1901 (Box 292)
      - Servants' wages ledger (Vol. 175), 1876-1883 (Box 292)
    - Pelham, Peter, 1806-1826; bills, receipts and accounts; 2 folders (Box 293)
    - Pell, Ferris (Vol. 176), 1824-1827; receipt book (Box 293)
    - Sherman, Caurnel, 1837-1845 (Box 293)
    - Sillcox, Charles P., 1843-1845 (Box 293)
    - Spencer, Milo, 1850-1854 (Box 293)
    - Storrow, Helen (Osborne)
      - Insurance policies for real estate, 1898-1901 (Box 293)
      - Trust account, 1936-1956 (Box 293)
    - Tobias, E.C., 1869-1870 (Box 293)
    - Wheeler, Cyrus, 1868; notebook regarding modifications to harvester machinery (Vol. 141) (Box 293)
    - Wright, Amos, 1827; farm inventory (Box 294)
    - Wright, David
      - Miscellaneous, 1839-1857
      - Bills and receipts, 1830-1860
      - Wage book (Vol. 177), 1860-1865
    - Wright, E. J. (Vol. 178), 1857 (Box 294)
    - [Unknown] ledger (Vol. 129) (Box 284)
      Likely the work of either Martha Coffin Pelham Wright, or Anna Folger Coffin. For more information, see memo in Finding Aids file.
- Legal records
  - General
    - Miscellaneous, 1856-1938 (Box 294)
    - Agnew, S. R. and A. G. McCaull to S. Brill: Deed, Cayuga County, N.Y., 1902-1904 (Box 294)
    - Agnew, W. and wife to J.D. Carhart: Deed, Cayuga County, N.Y., 1863 (Box 294)
    - Allen, A. to A. Gifford: Bond, 1847 (Box 294)
    - Allen, A. to F. Gildersleve: Bond, 1847 (Box 294)
    - Allen, C.T.: Parole, 1914 (Box 294)
    - Amerman, I. and wife to M. Smith: Deed, Cayuga County, N.Y., 1844 (Box 294)
    - Auburn, N.Y.
      - Land survey, undated (Box 294)
      - Lot descriptions, 1919 (Box 294)
      - Seymour Street School, 1890 (Box 294)
      - Street railway companies contracts and deeds, 1873-1880 (Box 294)
    - Auburn Gas Company to T.M. Osborne: Deed, Cayuga County, N.Y., 1907 (Box 294)
    - Auburn Hame Company: Mortgage, Cayuga County, N.Y., 1904-1905 (Box 294)
    - Averill, C.S. and G.F. Gregory to E.W. Osborne, T.M. Osborne, H. Osborne, and E.O. Harris: Mortgage, Cayuga County, N.Y., 1890 (Box 294)
    - Avery, A.: Will, 1843 (Box 294)
    - Backus, A. to M. Lynch and R. O'Connor: Deed, Cayuga County, N.Y., 1853-1858 (Box 294)
    - Badger, R.A. and S.H. Childs and Company: Agreement, 1898-1903 (Box 294)
    - Barber, D. and Company and A. Babbit: Agreement, 1849 (Box 294)
    - Beany, W. and A. Goodwin with Comstock and Dodge: Contract, Erie Canal commerce, 1852 (Box 294)
    - Beardsley, D. and wife: Memorandum of agreement, 1904 (Box 294)
    - Blood, J.P. and H.A. Blood to R. Wells: Indemnity bond, 1860 (Box 294)
    - Bogert, T.L. to Savings Bank of Utica: Mortgage assignment, Oneida County, N.Y., 1887 (Box 294)
    - Borden, I. to A. Avery: Bond, 1845 (Box 294)
    - Bostwick, J. with N. Alward: Agreement, 1845 (Box 294)
    - Bourden, A. to A. Avery: Bond, 1841 (Box 294)
    - Brown, F.: Opinion re the J. Osborne estate, 1842 (Box 294)
    - Brown, J. to A. Ferris: Mortgage, Tompkins County, N.Y., 1850 (Box 294)
    - Brush, S. and wife to J. Swan: Deed, Cayuga County, N.Y., 1824-1825 (Box 294)
    - Buel, M.T.: Will, 1899 (Box 294)
    - Buffalo Bi-Sulphite of Lime Works with Diamond Shading Film Company: Contract, 1906 (Box 294)
    - Burdick, C. to J. Curtis: Bond, 1855 (Box 294)
    - Burgess, D.: Will, 1851 (Box 294)
    - Burgess, G. to H. Scott: Bond, 1841 (Box 294)
    - Butler, John: Patents, Mowing and reaping machine, 1860-1871 (Box 294)
    - Cady Reservation: Lot map, undated (Box 294)
    - Carpentier and Dwight Properties for Southern Central Railroad Company: Appraisal, 1870 (Box 294)
    - Cartright, M. to E. Baldwin: Bond, 1850 (Box 294)
    - "Case Memorial" to Seymour Library Association, Cayuga County, N.Y.: Deed of gift, 1905 (Box 294)
    - Cayuga County, N.Y.: Sheriff's Certificate, 1843 (Box 294)
    - Cayuga County Bank: Mortgage, Cayuga County, N.Y., 1849-1850 (Box 294)
    - Cayuga Omnibus Corporation to City of Auburn, N.Y.: Petition, 1928-1929 (Box 294)
    - Chidester, Gardner and Sally to A. Foote: Deed, Cayuga County, N.Y., 1836-1837 (Box 295)
    - Clary, J. to E. Marvine: Bond, 1847 (Box 295)
    - Cowan, J. to W. Morgan: Mortgage, Cayuga County, N.Y., 1846 (Box 295)
    - Cowing, George: Patents, Cylinder polisher, 1865-1866 (Box 295)
    - Crofut, J. and wife to H. Shepard: Mortgage, Cayuga County, N.Y., 1853-1860 (Box 295)
    - Curtis, J. to Cayuga County National Bank: Mortgage, Cayuga County, N.Y., 1869 (Box 295)
    - Curtis, J. and wife to W.A. Kirby: Mortgage Cayuga County, N.Y., 1873 (Box 295)
    - Dale, S. and wife to D. Wright: Warranty deed, 1899 (Box 295)
    - Dean, W, M. Alden and W.J. Machau with Orrin H. Burdick, 1857 (Box 295)
    - Dehart, P. to R. Palmer: Mortgage, Cayuga County, N.Y., 1854 (Box 295)
    - Deshong, H.G.: Will and probate, 1838-1842 (Box 295)
    - Dillon, M. and wife to City of Auburn: Deed, Cayuga County, N.Y., 1904 (Box 295)
    - Disston, Henry: Patents, Power saw, 1868 (Box 295)
    - Dolphin Point Association and T.M. Osborne: Agreement, 1895 (Box 295)
    - Dolphin Point Association to C.I. Avery: Sale of steamboat, 1893 (Box 295)
    - Doty, Osborne and Ballard: Patents, Harvesting machine, 1869 (Box 295)
    - Doyle, J. against T.M. Osborne: Notice of lien, 1915 (Box 295)
    - Drummond, N.L. to T.M. Osborne: Deed, Cayuga County, N.Y., 1906-1910 (Box 295)
    - Eason, M.: Will, undated (Box 295)
    - East Genesee Street and Seward Avenue Railway: Incorporation, 1868-1880 (Box 295)
    - Egleston, L.: Patents, Cylinder polisher, 1867 (Box 295)
    - Equitable Life Assurance Society to W.A. Kirby: Mortgage, Cayuga County, N.Y., 1888 (Box 295)
    - Ferris, A. to S. Benjamin: Power of attorney, 1853 (Box 295)
    - Ferris, B.: Certificate concerning C. Bogert, 1821 (Box 295)
    - Fisher, H.: Patents, Reaper, 1864 (Box 295)
    - Foot, I. to E. Marsh: Lease, Cayuga County, N.Y., 1838 (Box 295)
    - Fowler, J. and Richardson Brothers: Patents, Grain binder, 1870-1893 (Box 295)
    - Fowler, W. and J. Makie to D. Wright: Deed, Putnam County, Fla., 1881 (Box 295)
    - Freeoff, P.R. to A. Miller and others: Mortgage, Cayuga County, N.Y., 1856 (Box 295)
    - Fuller, B. to J. Swan: Deed, Cayuga County, N.Y., 1825 (Box 295)
    - George Junior Republic: Incorporation, 1896 (Box 295)
    - George, W.R. and wife to George Junior Republic: Contract, 1912 (Box 295)
      Material relating to W. R. George restricted until 2020 at the request of Lithgow Osborne.
    - Gifford, S. to E. Marsh: Lease, Cayuga County, N.Y., 1838 (Box 295)
    - Gorter, Judge, J.P. to S.L. Richards: Parole, circa 1920 (Box 295)
    - Gridley, H.H. with Kreider, Zindgraf and Company: Contract, 1867 (Box 295)
    - Gridley, H.H.: Patents, Sawmills, 1867-1869 (Box 295)
    - Groton Assessors: Affidavit, 1867 (Box 295)
    - Harris, E.O. to E.W. Osborne: Deed, Cayuga County, N.Y., 1898 (Box 295)
    - Harris, E.O. and H.O. Storrow to T.H. Garrett Jr.: Lease, Cayuga County, N.Y., 1898-1899 (Box 295)
    - Harris, E.O. and H.O. Storrow to E.W. and T.M. Osborne: Deed, Oneida County, N.Y., 1902 (Box 295)
    - Harris, E.O. and H.O. Storrow to J. Wiggins: Lease, Cayuga County, N.Y., 1898 (Box 295)
    - Harvey, F.W. and wife to T.M. Osborne: Mortgage, Cayuga County, N.Y., 1900 (Box 295)
    - Henderson, W. and wife to J. Swan: Deed, Cayuga County, N.Y., 1808 (Box 295)
    - The Holstein-Friesian Association of America: Certificates of registry, Cattle, 1883-1888 (Box 295)
    - Hopkins, J.R. and wife to A. Sherwood: Mortgage, Cayuga County, N.Y., 1852 (Box 295)
    - Horton, S. to Keisler, J.: Bond, 1844 (Box 295)
    - Hough, I. to T.M. Osborne: Lease, Cayuga County, N.Y.., 1906-1907 (Box 295)
    - Howland, H.: Will, circa 1850 (Box 295)
    - Hoyt, H.L. (agent) to Harvey, A.M.: Lease Cayuga County, N.Y., 1904 (Box 295)
    - Hoyt, H.L. to Rea and Vosburgh: Lease, Cayuga County, N.Y., 1900 (Box 295)
    - Huffman, T. to S. Willits: Bond, 1839 (Box 295)
    - Hulton, H. and F. Wright:.Patents, Manufacturing Compound, 1871 (Box 295)
    - Hughett, W.E. to H.H. Gridley: Fees and costs, 1869 (Box 295)
    - Hurd, J.M.: Patents, Flour sacks, 1871 (Box 295)